Okay. Uh, let me ask you this.
(Sheldon:)When I learn that I'm a robot...
(Sheldon:)...would I be bound by
Asimov's Three Laws of Robotics?
(Raj:)You might be bound by them right now.
(Howard:)That's true.
- Have you ever harmed a human being?
- Of course not.
(Howard:)Have you ever harmed yourself,
except in cases where a human being...
(Howard:)...would have been endangered?
(Sheldon:)- Well, no.
- I smell robot.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Internet's been down for half an hour.
(Raj:)Also, Sheldon may be a robot.
So how did it go with Leslie?
(Leonard:)Oh, we tried kissing,
but the Earth didn't move.
(Leonard:)I mean, any more than the 383 miles
that it was gonna move anyway.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I've seen that look before.